Come Back Doraemon
Once more!
Okay, here's my turn!
Oh!
Okay, it's my turn!
Nobita, wait a minute!
Giant, I have said Sorry!
I have said sorry. NO!
Wait, Nobita!
Ouch, ouch...
Nobita, I'll remember this!
I'll pound you to pulp when I see you next time!
Bleh, I ain't scared at all!
I'll be sure to pay you back!
I ain't scared of nothing when I have Doraemon by my side.
Hey, Doraemon.
Here you are.
Lemme borrow that...
The one you lent me earlier, remember?
The gadget that makes me good at fighting!
Stop picking fights that you can never win!
Hey, Doraemon.
What's gotten into you?
Nobita-kun, actually...
we need to talk, so sit down.
Come on, say something!
Okay!
M-hmm.
What's the matter? Doraemon!
Nobita-kun, I was meaning to say this from a few days... but I couldn't....
Tell me.
In fact...
Just spill it out...
What's the matter?
Suddenly, I must go back!
Go where?
The future, of course!
Going home?
No, no, no!
You just can't go home now.
Dad, mom, please do something.
But what is the matter?
Doraemon...
He's going back to the future world!
When?
Tomorrow, at the earliest!
No, no!
Mom, please stop him hurry up!
Nobita, Doraemon must have his own circumstances, so be reasonable!
Don't wanna!
Nobita, You'll never grow up,...
if you always rely on him!
Be a man!
Nobita-kun!
No!
NO!
I hate Doraemon very much!
We will feel lonely if Dora-chan leaves, I admit!
Yeah, Doraemon takes care of our Nobita.
Not at all...
Here, have these..
Thank you, Nobita-kun!!
Then I'll have 'em!
It's very delicious, it brings tears to my eyes!
Doraemon!
-Nobita-kun!.
Are you still up?
I can't fall asleep!
Nether can I!
Let's chat 'till morning!
Sure, good ideal
That's that...
What?
This portion will keep us from getting tired.
Here, have one.
The full moon looks so beautiful!
Bamboo 'copter!
This is the last time, that I'll get to fly with you like this.
Nobita-kun.
OK, Doraemon, let's race..
But...Nobita-kun, will you be OK?
What?
I never wanted to go back, if I had a choice.
I'm still so worried about you.
Doraemon.
Can you do your homework on your own?
Can you hit Giant and Suneo back?
Don't worry about such things, I can manage!
Do you still worry about this kind of thing?
I promise you that I'll manage everything on my own, so you can go back in ease.
Nobita-kun.
Doraemon.
Let's go take a walk in the park.
I'll go on ahead!
Doraemon!
He didn't wanted me to see him in all tears.
He's such a good-hearted guy!
Hey, Doraemon.
I wodner where have you gone?
Who's there at this hour?!
It's Giant
He sleep-walks into park sometimes!
I'll play with you.
No response at all!
Let me try again!
Hey, Giant, here I am.
Who is speaking there?
Oh, it's Nobita!
How dare you see me sleepwalking!
Damn you!
Unforgivable!
Doraemon!
I heard someone calling me!
Hey, Nobita!
Giant, wait a minute!
What now?
You can't escape from me!
Okay! Please listen to me!
Nobita-kun!
Nobita-kun!, where are you?
Nobita, what's the big idea?
GIant, wait a minute! Let's resume our fight after Doraemon goes home.
You are very thoughtful!
But just remember this, I won't hold off!
What's the matter?
You are all but talks, huh?
No way!
You are all but talks!
Take that!
DId he head home?
Nobita-kun!!
He isn't home neither!
Got'cha!
Had enough? Bye!
Wait a minute!
I haven't lost.
What? Do you want more?
What? I'm just getting started!
Damn you!
Come on!
It's been an hour already...
Wonder where he's and what he's up to.
He makes me worried till the very end...
Had enough?
No matter how many times we fight, the result is the same!
Listen carefully, Nobita!
Don't be silly, give it up!
Don't be absurd, Nobita.
I gotta beat you on my own...
Doraemon...
Doraemon, he can't go home in peace.
Damn it...
There's ambulance. I'll have a look.
Nobita-kun!
I give up, you win!
Doraemon, I beat him!
Did you see that, Doraemon?
I beat Giant by myself!
By myself...
I see!
Doraemon, you can go back to the future world in ease!
Right, Doraemon?
Doraemon.
Do you drool!?
Nobita-kun, take care! Don't be rash!
Doraemon!
Nobita, come down for breakfast!
OK!
Doraemon, after you have left, my room feels so empty.
But I'll get used to it in no time.
So, please don't worry about it!
Nobita.
Nobita, what are you doing?
Suneo is calling you!
I'm very busy now~!
What's the matter with you? You're just so lazy!
Remember your promise to Dora-chan!?
That you'd be all right by yourself?
OK, Nobita, cheer up!
What am I doing?
This isn't helping.
In any case, Doraemon won't
come back again~!
OK, I should be happy from now on!
Suneo, long time no see!
Nobita, can you help me?
What's up?
Actually...
I found a Tsuchinoko.
A Tsuchinoko!?
That mythological serpent?
That's a very big discovery!
Yeah, I couldn't catch it by myself!
Can you help me to catch it?
Sure, no problem!
Where is it?
It's in the lot!
Here?
Sh!
You chased it down to this pipe?
Poke it with a stick over there, I'll catch it over here!
I see!
I'll use this...
Drive it!
Got 'ya.
Nobita!
Nobita, you are here!
Listen to me calmly!
What's the matter, Giant?
Care to guess who I just saw?
Listen to me carefully!
Doraemon.
Mom, where is he...?
What? Dora-chan come back?
He came back!
He won't come back, will he?
He have said that he won't
come back again!
I heard that...
Nobita, enough with jokes.
Strange! Why don't you let me see him?
I see!
He must be shy to see so quickly!
He was very heart-struck when
he left after all!
Bastard!
I don't mind that!
I want to see him as soon as possible
really!
Yeah!
I take out all of my saving
and buy the Rice Cracker for me!
He must be very happy!
He was deceived!
How about my idea?
I'm defeated by you really!
Look...
April Fools' Day!
He was deceived actually!!
It's very easy to cheat Nobita!
Cause he is too naive!
How can you do that?!
What do you want to do?
Nobody will get angry on
April Fools' Day!
You can tell a lie too.
Ah, there are ghosts behind you,
the first one is a little monk!
So naive lie!
Nobita can only say this kind of lie!
Ah, big monster...big orang...big dinosaur!
Let's go, that's fool!
There is a robot!
It's true...It's true!
I think it of!
When I'm not here,
you can open this
and get what you want
if you can't solve something!
It's will come forth really!
It seems that it's medicine!
It says Lie 800.
All of your words will be lie
after you take it!
It's very suitable for
the April Fools' Day!
OK!
I won't forgive them!
For me, the idea that "Doraemon is back here" is the most cruel and mean lie.
Nobita's here, all fired up!
Got some pathetic jokes on your sleeve?
What is it?
Just speak it out!
The weather's very fine, today.
That's a lie?
The rain is pouring in fiercely!
What are you doing?
It's the April Fools' Day,
so I can tell a lie!
It will rain if you say that it's very sunny today!
On the contrary, it will be sunny!
You are a bad guy really!
Then, what shall i lie?
Yeah, you are the first one...
NO! Nobita!
You won't get bitten by a dog, Never!
Hey, no!
Help me! I'm scared of dogs!
NO, ow..! NO!
Help me!
It's your turn now, Giant-kun!
No! No! Nobita!
You'll be really, really praised by your mother for an hour.
Nobita, I beg you, please forgive me...
Takeshi, are you there?
No, mommy...
Hey! No running away...
I'm home!
Did you find Doraemon?
Doraemon?
No way.
Doraemon won't be coming back!
I can never see him again!
Doraemon.
Nobita.
But, why...?
I don't know why I come here suddenly!
But, but...
It's very unimaginable!
I don't understand why, neither!
Ah, you must have drank the Liar Liar Liqiuid!
You said that I won't be coming back, don't you?
I'm not happy at all.
I don't want to live with Doraemon like this!
I'm really not happy!
I want to part with Doraemon!